

László Mónus

LASTI OMONIUS COM

OBJECTIVE

A self-motivated IT professional with a master's degree in computer engineering, a twelve-year career in Information Technology as analyst and project and team manager. Also recently having experience in programming using JavaScript, React, Node.js and Express.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Nationality

Hungarian

Address

Hungary, Budapest, VI.

CONTACT

- aszlo.monus@gmail.com
- +36-30/571-3728
- https://laszlomonus.com/
- nttps://www.linkedin.com/in/laszlomonus
- https://github.com/monuslaci

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full stack developer

JANGALA 2021.03-

Responsible for creating a webshop using React and Node.js. Responsibilities include analysing the needs of the client, creating the system desing and developing the backend and the frontend.

Web programmer

RUNBNB.HU 2020.11-2021.03

Responsible for creating and designin the back-end for the website in Node.js based on the requirements of the business owner.

Business Line Manager

LOXON SOLUTIONS ZRT

2016.01-2020.12

Responsible for the effective delivery of the projects, the overall professional performance of the analysts. Take part in projects as a professional supervisor, help the lead business analysts, product owners, and the analyst team. Act as an escalation point in the projects. Responsible for the financial, and operational resource planning of the line. **Achievements**: During this period all closed projects in the line were successfully finished.

Project Manager

LOXON SOLUTIONS ZRT

2014.01-2015.12

Coordination and management of preparation, planning, executing, testing, and launching strategic projects. Coordination of the whole consultant-, analyst-, architect- and developer-team to implement projects successfully. **Achievements**: Successfully managed the introduction of the collection system in MKB Bank.

Senior Business Consultant

LOXON SOLUTIONS ZRT

2013.01-2013.12

Responsible for client communication throughout the projects, conducting workshops, supporting the consultants in the team. Also took part in presales activities and held demo sessions. **Achievements:**Successfully managed the introduction of the collection system in MKB Union Bank (BG) as a lead consultant

Business Consultant

LOXON SOLUTIONS ZRT.

2012.08-2012.12

Perform structured requirement and system analysis and effort estimations. Elaborate detailed mappings for interfaces. Achievements: Took part in the process assessment and created the processes for the introduction of the collection system in HCI Vietnam. Successfully managed the go-live procedure on-site.

IT Project Manager

BUDAPEST BANK (GE MONEY)

2011.01-2012.07

Coordinate the projects from IT point of view. Formulating the project plan to meet the objectives of the project in terms of budget and timeline. Coordinating activities across multiple departments.

Achievements: Successfully managed the 'Server-side office 2010 upgrade' project.

System Analyst

BUDAPEST BANK (GE MONEY)

2008.07-2010.12

Analyzing the needs of the business, coming up with solutions to business problems, specification of the changes, driving the implementation, testing, and manage the go-live procedure.

EDUCATION

 Major of Computer Engineering (MSc) INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY FACULTY

PÁZMÁNY PÉTER KATOLIKUS EGYETEM

2003-2008

MAIN SUBJECTS: PROGRAMMING (C++, JAVA), DATABASES (SQL), ROBOTICS

LANGUAGES, TECHNOLOGIES

Javascript

React

Node.js

DATABASES, VERSION CONTROL

SQL (MsSQL, Oracle)

MongoDB

Git

Express, EJS, Mongoose